# About me

I am an engineering student and a +1 year of experience full-stack web developer who has not stopped training since an early age. To date, I have overcome very diverse obstacles and challenges that have forged my experience and reflect my dedication.

## Education

**Universidad Nacional Arturo Jauretche** 

Feb. 2024 - Present

Informatic Engineer
Redis University

Florencio Varela, Buenos Aires

April 2024

RU101: Introduction to Redis Data Structures

Online

E.E.S.T. N°7 "José Hernández"

March 2020 - Dec. 2023

Technical Degree in Programming

Avellaneda, Buenos Aires

ANGULAR + NEST.JS

July. 2023
Online

EducaciónIT

Sept. 2022

.Net Framework for web development

Online

# **Skills**

SoloLearn

- Programming languages: JavaScript, C#, HTML/CSS, SQL, SCSS, TypeScript
- Frameworks: ASP.NET, Angular
- Technologies: Git, MySQL, REST API, .NET, Linux, JWT, Entity Framework, Unit Testing, Redis
- Others: English, Xunit, DDD, SOLID, Postman, Clean Architecture

# Experience

## Frontend developer

2023-2024

- Developed interesting interactive websites alongside a different team for each project.
- improved the company's website perception by 60%.

#### Website for a non-profit organization

2023-2023

- Developed a dynamic full-stack web application for a non-profit organization using HTML/SCSS, JavaScript, SQL, and PHP.
- Developed a REST API using PHP and secured POST, PUT, and DELETE requests using JWT (JSON Web Token).
- Improved security by using Hash + salt for administrator credentials.
- developed a responsive website taking into account potential accessibility challenges.
- Developed an abstraction to facilitate the use of API requests.

# **Projects**

#### **FakeStoreAPI**

- Developed an API for an eCommerce using ASP.NET and hexagonal architecture, following the principles of a clean architecture.
- Wrote unit tests for all layers of the system using Xunit.

### **CRUD ASP.NET MVC**

• Developed a database manager using the MVC pattern and REST API and Razor.

#### Windows web clone

- Developed a Windows 7 web clone with functional apps using Angular.
- Developed a window system with all the main functionality of the operating system.